Eduardo Molina

11401 Dr M.L.K Jr St N Apt 2006 St. Petersburg, FL 33716

M: +1 (786) 567-2231

edmolina.solutions@gmail.com

www.edmolina.com

Profile

After working in Aviation Maintenance for over six years, I decided to take on a new challenge. With existing interest in creativity and engineering, I realized contributing to a field that delivers solutions that grow businesses, automate complex tasks, and provides data to the masses was the right way to go. Now a highly motivated Full Stack Web Developer eager to learn and grow within the Software Development field. I am ready to join a team and make a positive impact.

Experience

Full Stack Web Developer; St. Petersburg, Florida – 2021-Present

Took a full-time approach to become a self-taught Full Stack Web Developer by taking online courses and developing full-stack projects with newly learned technologies.

QC Inspector, Heico Aerostructures; Miami, Florida – 2018-2020

Responsible for performing tear-down inspections, in-process inspections, and final inspections on aerostructures to ensure conformity with manufacturer specifications. In addition, as the team leader of the travel team. I oversaw repairs performed on aerostructures while ensuring conformity to manufacturer specifications. And communication between customers, engineering teams, and management.

Radome Testing Unit Operator, Heico Aerostructures; Miami, Florida - 2016-2018

In charge of Radio Transmissivity inspections on Nose Radom. Which often Required troubleshooting to assess any discrepancies found during testing. While not testing, I applied periodic maintenance to the test unit. In addition, I managed to coordinate with shop managers and repair technicians to schedule cure oven times.

Structures Repair Technician, Heico Aerostructures; Miami, Florida – 2014-2016

Tasked with performing minor and major repairs on sheet metal and composite structures while keeping track of all materials and processes. All repairs performed required following instructions supplied by the manufacturer or an on-site engineering team.

Education

The Modern React Bootcamp - Colt Steele, 2021
The Bootstrap 4 Bootcamp - Colt Steele, 2021
The Web Developer Bootcamp - Colt Steele, 2021
CS50x - David J. Malan, 2021
George T. Baker - Aircraft Technician, 2017

Skills

Javascript, React JS, Node JS, Express JS, EJS, SQL, MongoDB, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap 4 & 5, SCSS, Git.